So,
I'm going to give you this informal
platform,
which I need to assign the camera,
just so I can verify that you've done it.
Take a look through it.
It should be pretty obvious to you what's
going on.
Remember that you always can just say no
if you don't want to answer a question,
and I'm not going to press you to do it.
I don't think any of the questions are
super personal, so...
I'm fine with this generally.
You can choose also to just say I don't
want to print it anymore,
but I want my data to be deleted up until
the point I anonymize the data.
When I anonymize the data,
then it's in my report and there's
nothing.
If you anonymize my name and the data,
I'm fine with it. Yeah.
There's no issue.
Would you mind being called like [pseudonym]
with a different phone or?
You can say [pseudonym] is fine. That's fine.
Okay.
Don't worry about nobody's the only
person reading this is my professor.
Of course.
Yes, I agree to the slide.
That looks like.
What?
Right.
Okay, okay.
So I need to make them the ones that are
arbitrary from the data.
Yeah, said they just stole the secret.
I trust you for that. Yeah, it should.
City OneDrive,
so if City gets data breached,
we're all screwed. Like, like everywhere,
something on this, I think, and then,
but it's gonna be a bit more on people's
can be sent to e-mail.
And...
Uh, but I think that's on your, you know.
Play Raheem.
Thanks.
I mean, it's just a formality, yeah.
I have.
Okay.
OK, thank you so much. So, so many lines.
Always not with some bad.
And.
Okay.
Yeah.
Hey, lovely, started. So, okay,
I won't get an understanding of how you
study, because this is...
Well, Moodle has a lot of friction,
I would say. Like,
there is a lot of clicking buttons you
need to do to get Moodle to work properly.
I think that's like the biggest
comparison that we're going to be able to
draw, like,
between the app that I'm going to be
designing, okay, and Moodle, yeah,
which is the standard, I guess. So...
Good afternoon. Yes,
I'm sure you're ready to brief.
I'm here to interview you.
This should take roughly 20 minutes,
depending on how much time we have to
talk one another.
Don't worry if you overrun.
If I feel like you're getting off topic,
I'm going to drag you back a little bit,
but don't worry about that.
That'll be fine.
I'm going to be doing requirements
gathering about.
a new application that's going to help me
study, hopefully. Alan,
can you sign the consent form,
but it's okay if I also question you, say,
I don't want to answer this.
I'm going to be recording this,
I'm sure you've already seen.
But you can also request not to delete it
like newly alter if you feel like I've
lost your questions that have forced you
to answer a certain one.
I don't feel comfortable with it. So,
and it's also being transcribed,
so you may or may not be able to see them,
so that I have to type it out and listen
to the recordings later. Okay,
so now that it was completed,
I'm going to get started.
So I'm mixing you with like...
I'm gonna start you with a really easy
question. Okay, this semester,
what modules have you been doing?
I've had design engineering,
data analysis.
As the rest of it, uh, mechatronics,
and there was the last one.
Last one, I know I have, no, yeah,
sensors, that was the last one.
That was a full engineering society.
I forgot about that one. It's so useless,
and always better than Nick. Yeah, no,
it's 'cause I interviewed a lot of
students, yeah.
Very nice.
So,
I'm going to ask you to rank them in
difficulty. One is the hardest,
5 is the easiest.
I will say the hardest will be
mechatronics. The first week it was okay,
because it was not very calculus,
it was mostly logical circuit was working.
So that was pretty fine,
but that it went way out to calculation,
mostly physics, which was very bad,
all of us are very bad.
Like the two toils at the end that went
to hours straight to the bridge. Yeah. OK,
that's the hardest one.
What's the next hardest?
I would say maybe data, data analysis.
Yeah, okay. At the beginning is fine,
it's just basic,
it's just basic data analysis calculation
we know,
but then it gets into machine learning,
which would be way harder. Sure, yeah.
After it.
Will be.
Ohh,
I didn't even remember when we done this
sentence.
I would say maybe census,
the issue is that it was just the first
part of it, were totally off topic for us.
Sure. But the other part was, yes,
pretty easy. I'm going to lie,
just your formulas, just apply it.
It's hard in a way to be focused.
Learning it and not telling yourself,
I am doing this. Sure, yeah,
that makes sense.
Then it will be the design,
and then it was lots of fun. Technically,
it's hard. So,
would you say the fun factor made it feel
less hard? Yeah,
definitely less hard and both,
so so much easier because we don't have
an exam at the end,
so you don't need to learn next,
but you have a project who was...
Al.
But if it was so interesting to learn
this module, no exam,
it's just coursework, yeah,
but then I have to do this interview.
Hunt.
So, um,
you said magnetronics was very physics
heavy.
Would you say it's also very maths heavy,
or is that kind of just hand in hand?
It's the hand in hand.
Physics and mathematics,
that's just calculation. Yeah,
would you say the difficulty was plugging
the numbers into the equations,
or figuring out which equations should
you use, or? Which equation to use?
I remember some equations.
How many of them and the logic behind it
too, because math, at the end,
in the the thing in math,
they just give you the formulas.
If you know the formula, just apply it,
you don't really need to change it that
much. The physics are problems,
you need to think it,
take the formula and change it completely
to have the results you want.
the real world. Yeah. Okay, cool.
That makes sense.
Would you say that you use Moodle a lot
for like the study materials for these?
Yeah,
we don't really have the choice because
everything's on Moodle,
all the lectures or papers we want to do.
So what I'm doing normally is I use
Moodle.
To show the lectures,
and since I really don't like how it's
written,
there's not enough colours for me.
I'm just rewriting that myself. Ohh, wow,
yeah, OK.
I haven't done this semester yet,
because sure, laziness,
so I guess you do most of your vision
like closer to the exam time.
where you'll be writing out notes like
this.
Last semester I was doing week by week,
but this semester I haven't done it,
but I'm planning to do it most of the
next week. Yeah.
Because for data analysis,
it's just formulas you're applying and
for sensors is the same,
so it's very easy. Sure.
But to make that one, you need to make it.
Further down more nodes, etcetera.
Would you say there's a specific part of
the micronics struggle, like,
for instance, the hydraulics, pneumatics,
or the control engineering parts?
The logic behind it is easy.
I can easily map it down how the system
is working. It's just...
If they're asking some calculation behind
it, is there a struggle right? OK,
because, as I said,
you need to remember all the formulas and
to know where to apply and you should
need to change it. Yeah, makes sense. OK,
so I'm gonna go to the next topic.
This is gonna be very broad.
When you study,
do you like follow some sort of schedule,
like every day from 4:00 to 6:00 through
the next module or? I'm trying to do. OK,
I'm just in front of my computer and the
issue is my computer is also when I'm
relaxing, yeah, so I often.
Diverge into just not working, yeah,
like context switches, sure.
Do you try to block out time to like,
do I really need to get this piece of
work done for like 2 days later?
I'm gonna set 2 hours now to get that
done. Do you do that kind of thing?
I'm trying to do,
I'm just trying to order in certain hours.
Yeah, and after certain hours, like, yeah,
that was fine, I finished. So, like,
for instance,
you're starting from 9 to 5 or 9 to 7,
and then outside of that,
it's like free time, so yeah, after four,
yeah, OK, that makes sense.
In the evening,
I refuse to work during the evening, yeah,
that makes sense. It's dead.
I'll just call ask me, yeah, yeah, same.
How do you prioritise your modules?
Would you say that you make more time for
your difficult modules? Yeah,
definitely more time for the most
difficult because...
The thing is,
when you need to learn and is having
calculation best,
you need to also do the exercise.
Those exercises take a lot of time to
actually get how it's working,
get out the logic.
So I need to put way more time into those.
Yeah, that makes sense.
Do you have like different revision
strategies based on the module?
Like,
suddenly the only really strategic
diagnosis is learning by how to exercise,
which is very bad,
but so you just span the exercise until
you effectively got out on walk, yeah,
yeah,
I mean the exercise and also be something
to remember the formulas next to my
computer I have.
A panel, well just put, and sorry,
what word is that? No,
it's just a piece of wood,
a piece of wood.
And you put formulas on that. Ohh, yeah,
OK. I see the port port. I'll go with it.
Would you mind showing us the camera,
because I think this is like super full,
super...
Useful.
If not, you can just send it to me,
like I will send it to you,
and I will definitely note this down as
part of my research,
because this is how I'm supposed to be
using like you guys' context, by the way.
I will send you my mail,
but here you can see you have the
interest of my room, yeah, here global,
and right here you have my PC, yeah,
but every time passing,
I just can just read this and that keeps
getting your context.
That's a lovely way to study.
OK,
so do you have like a sort of like system
where you sort your materials per topic?
Like I noticed, yeah,
each call has a different topic.
If I remember the green were mostly
physics and electronics. Yeah,
it was the last semester,
I don't remember.
It, it was mostly physics,
that's why I'm pretty new to them minimal,
so I put it together, yeah,
and those from different things, wow,
as you see, you can see, yeah, yeah,
this is great. OK,
I have to put colours and this is unique
because most people are just using like
online tools where they're just throwing
their own noodle, like...
papers and saying, right, okay,
let's try and make flashcards for this,
you know, like you've heard of IMT,
I'm pretty sure. No. Okay, well,
it's like a sort of tool. So,
how do you feel about Moodle,
like offering your study materials?
Do you feel like it's hard to access like
your study?
We have so many clicks and the issue.
They don't feel that bit;
it's just so many things sometimes.
But most of the time and the other
problem is lecturer don't organise it the
same way. So you need to adapt each time.
And some people have put the whole
lecture in one PowerPoint. Yeah,
it was electronics last semester,
it was 300 pages long, so at the end,
you're just like,
I don't know what to go through that,
it's too long. When you look at it,
you just get intimidated,
if that makes sense.
Do you use any like web applications or
like applications on your phone to help
you study, or do you prefer the like?
paper hard in style.
I prefer double style. Yeah,
so I can just write it down.
I'm very old school on that side.
Actually, totally fine. Like,
I like to have a new perspective. Yeah.
So,
when you say that this is more effective
than just going through Moodle,
like the slides,
would you have you ever tried using like
digital study assistants?
No, never. I never thought of using it.
I've never been interested into it or
never had the idea to use online tools to
make it. That makes sense.
I never looked at it. OK.
Presumably you use some AI to explain
things to you. I did that myself because.
So, like the size,
the lecturer don't give you the procedure
to find it. The work example. Yeah,
the work example.
So I had to use AI to explain me how to
find it. How did you find that?
Do you think it was effective?
It was pretty effective, yeah.
Because to understand what you get
something,
you need to understand the logic.
Yeah,
which phone to use and that's only proper
one to get.
Do you want to add that to your normal
workflow, like an AI that, for instance,
can take a problem and show you the work
example?
That's what that would be pretty nice if
it's integrated,
but what I'm scared is AI just code.
Got the calculation totally wrong. Yeah,
show you the right result,
but not just the right way to get it
right.
That would be like the worst worst of
both worlds, really. Yes, yeah. OK,
that makes sense. All right,
so we discussed a little bit about your
structure.
What makes a good study space and what
makes a bad study space? So,
this is like when you're showing me for
like...
I presume that helps me make it a better
study space because the context of things
are more geared towards studying.
So you say the computer when you're on
your computer, it's a little bit tough.
Why would you say that?
Because I'm playing all the time on my
computer. It's just in my.
I guess when we're all going into how a
brain is working,
it's since I'm playing all the time on my
computer because it's a gaming computer,
I wait for it.
My brain is just in gaming mode. Right,
so it's hard to pull your context onto a
study.
Yeah, your brain just thinks about,
I want to go play XYZ game, right? OK,
that makes sense.
Do you do most of your studies in front
of this computer? Yeah,
everything in front of my computer,
because I don't have this space anyway,
or I don't want to go in the living room,
because my father is always in the living
room.
What about do you study here? Prince,
you actually? Oh,
there is Touraj University.
I must have some friends.
The City University site. Yeah,
but actually, yeah, yeah,
we're all living very far from university.
For me,
it's taking me 40 to 50 minutes to come
here, so...
I'm pretty lazy to come here for that.
I prefer to stay home at the end and my
place, my mom's coming time, two times,
give me some treats while I'm working,
which is nice. That makes sense.
All right,
so do you find yourself more productive
when you're like...
able to get your hard copy notes in front
of your computer where you're reading it
off, or would you say that, like,
do you do any sort of digital studies,
like where you're typing notes and,
or is it just all hard?
I tried with digital,
and the issue I find with digital is I
was not listening.
Not listening, learning, anything, right?
OK, write it down. Yeah, write it down,
help in way more,
and it was this has to do this by hand.
Is that being mean way more than just
write it down? Yeah, that makes sense.
Very, very old school.
If your desk gets cluttered,
do you find it's harder to study,
or do you try to keep a clean desk?
My desk gets cleaner and cleaner every
time I add something to it,
so it's getting better. In the worst case,
I'm just using my bed,
who's just behind me.
You just take it off and, yeah, OK,
so we organise your study space, you know,
sir. My desk is here, my bed is refracted,
so I can just turn it and put everything
here. Right, that makes sense.
But you can't study their stuff on your
desk, right?
Yeah, I have my keyboard.
I will take my keyboard and put it on the
side. My space is large enough.
Would you say when you get distracted by
like noises, like for instance,
if there's a bird nearby,
if there's somebody in your family making
noise? It's calm. Well,
normally it's pretty fine.
What's on the only this?
What's normally?
Not helping me to focus,
it's just my like, hey,
cheque your messages, hey, here, right,
so it's not disturb,
it's not like pretty thoughtful, OK,
so it's like pop ups, but you got,
not even pop up because my phone is,
I don't know, I'll just like,
I need to cheque my messages, right?
It's time two times, it's just,
it's a tablet, yes, it's just...
Just a habit would force me to do that.
That makes sense. Okay.
Do you have a preferred time of day that
you want to study? I would say June.
The morning, I'm so bad at studying.
But after lunch, after two,
I'm pretty good. Okay.
Just 6, sure, yeah, that's your best time.
Do you say, well,
you say you get distracted by your
computer? Sure, I can do that last.
You've run to do this by going to
hardcover notes.
Would you say this has been an effective
solution for you? Pretty much,
but I'm just using both the mixture
because I still match the lecture or
exercise on the screen.
But then if your keyboard's moved,
you can't easily distract yourself, right?
Yeah, and the keyboard,
because now my before the keyboard was in
front of me.
Yeah, but now I can't put in front of me,
I have to put it off to side. Yeah,
that makes sense. Okay, cool.
Let's now talk about your actual study
session, right? So,
you've mentioned that you often work
alone. Yeah,
I wanna talk a little bit about when you
work with others.
What is the context in which you will
deviate from your working alone and work
with others?
Maybe group projects, right? Yeah,
it's only that we already work and I'm
already working with someone,
and then when it's very rare. So,
what kind of is it like a call,
for instance? Yeah, call,
call on this call. For example,
the other day it was with...
I don't know if I can language it,
but it was with Herman.
We should make the call and we were
working together. Yeah, that makes sense.
Which was pretty effective at the end,
and normally I don't really work with
some group projects. Yeah,
that makes sense.
Do you prefer to work with others when
you bought a group project,
or do you do you just prefer to say?
Hey, we have this done.
Can you do this part?
Well, the last two group projects,
since I was a group later,
I was just telling people,
can you do this and this,
and they would have mostly doing it. So,
at the end, I only experienced this one,
and sure, really effective. Sure.
How often do you say that you got your
ideal study session?
where, like, for instance,
you don't get distracted.
We say that often, not often.
I will say, maybe.
Sixty percent of the time, yeah,
because at the end...
At the end of the day, for three.
Good enough. I wish to tell myself, yeah,
I did good today. I'm happy.
If I haven't done it, I will feel guilty.
I can label the cult. Fair enough.
Do you like to eat while your studies?
Like, for instance, crisps, finger food,
chocolates. You like chocolate? Yeah,
I like chocolate. It's my mom just said.
It's just my mom coming and say, hey,
you did well. You have some chocolate.
Yeah, I mean,
that doesn't factor into your location
choice. You always study at your desk.
Yeah.
Would you say that your mother coming in
with chocolate distracts you while you're
studying?
Or do you think it's just it brings your
mood up and makes you study harder?
Brings your mood up and study harder.
Okay, that makes sense.
It's the mother love for me to use inhale
a little something. Hi, this is like,
thanks, I love you. Yeah,
that makes sense.
How do you track what you did in a study
session?
Do you have like a checklist somewhere
where you're like saying lecture one,
lecture 2, lecture 3, cheque them off or?
I'm just keeping in my mind,
basically I'm just giving you.
I'm trying to give me a goal every day to
do. Yeah. Like few goals.
If I achieve them,
I'm just extremely happy.
How do you track the goals?
How do you choose what to do?
Just telling me in advance, like,
I'm doing, I'm going to do sessions one,
two and three. If I do them, I'll be,
yeah, good, I'm happy.
If I have more time,
I will try to do more. But generally,
I can't really do more.
Let's say you've said to yourself,
you're getting sessions one, two,
and three. Yeah.
Let's say one and two were really tough.
Would you say, okay, it's fine,
I didn't get to 3 today,
or would you push on and try to get to
your third?
I think it was tough and I worked a lot.
I will say, okay, that's fine for today.
I did good.
But if I've seen the one and two were
easy and just ready to do the third,
I will feel guilty.
I will come back to it.
So you are a little bit flexible,
but only when you feel like you're done
enough. Right, okay, that makes sense.
I want you to like walk me through a
study section.
So I know you don't have your computer
here, but that's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Let's say we've got notes on Moodle.
Let's say you're trying to revise for
your mechatronics module, right? Yeah.
How do you choose receptions?
You can like...
After now, I'm going to call it, whatever.
The thing I will do is just going, yeah,
that I know exercise up most of the
grades, so...
The first thing we now work is the
lecture one, then lecture 2, lecture 3,
etc.
I will look at it and have the exercise
next to it and try to find some in
between them. So you say exercises,
do you mean like the tutorials? Yeah,
tutorials. Yeah, okay, sure.
But most tutorials.
And if I have no,
if you can see if there's no link between
them, it's only logical. I would say,
that's fine, I can, I can just learn,
and I would be good.
If I see that some calculation,
I have a daughter,
I will try to find a solution inside you
lectures notes, which never happens.
So, and after I was just like, okay,
now I'm gonna struggle for five hours
trying to find how to make it.
Since I have two screen,
I can just project the lecture on one
screen and the tutorial on the other one,
or...
I'll see what I'm doing is the tutorials
or AI or anything else and the main thing
on the main screen in front of me. Sure,
yeah,
and I always have one table open for
YouTube, I guess for music. Yeah,
that's actually something else.
Have you ever used YouTube to explain how
to do certain problems?
Yes, pretty often, actually.
Remember, for last semester,
I used it so often to explain it in a lot.
It's really the Tracey of the Indian guy
who explained things like Soleymani
Academy, right? Really useful,
or I don't really use kind of like
academy and just using the 1st results
and wish help.
I remember that guy who explained me.
Do you take notes while you're watching
these videos?
Not necessarily, OK. Ohh, maybe, yeah,
actually I did it, so make some sense.
I don't know.
Okay.
I never remember,
I have to leave some more.
I was able to explain the very
complicated.
Okay.
Backwards.
It was now.
Yeah.
I have the guy for this number.
Eigenvalues and, yes, like I did already,
so I just copied it, right? Yeah, okay,
so here you find like the determining
matrix and you can see normally I'm just
writing in blue, yeah,
the red is just to highlight very
important stuff and pencil.
Are full into nodes, so,
so less important, yeah, for it, OK, yeah,
awesome, OK.
In your study settings,
what's something that you, you know,
you struggle with the context switching,
because sometimes you're playing games on
the same machine,
which causes you to think, yeah,
and then also like solving to,
I need to cheque my messages, etcetera.
Is there anything else that we haven't
really covered?
Losing my sight from YouTube.
What's the time? Yeah,
I guess if you watch a YouTube video
that's educational,
somebody sees something, oh,
that looks interesting. Yeah.
I went to a bad video today.
I'm watching it and at the end,
and that's really nothing. All right,
that makes sense. All right, is there?
Anything else that you'd like to add that
we haven't covered with regard to your
study habits? Yeah,
maybe since I'm living with my parents,
my mom,
when she's sometimes just proposed me to
go out for like half an hour,
an hour to go and walk. Yeah,
and that's actually very helpful.
Please stop thinking about just talking.
I thought I was just walking.
That's actually have way more than I
thought this would be.
It helps you bear your mind.
I go cycling for the same thing.
So I think it's a really good thing. Yeah,
OK, so really love it.
I'm holding him back down and also very
thankful to have my mom because she's
working. I'm just helping you on the side.
Yeah, but she's doing the cooking and.